A block that doesn't scare the crap out of you isn't a real block at all.
Who knew a setter would be an even more terrifying blocker than Four Eyes over there?
I don't want to stop this situation.
Yeah.
Oh
It went in soft
The ball is back in Inanizaki's court
Inanizaki's number 10 is going for it
You've got this Karasuno Buster dude
This is Rintaro Tsuna's quick
This lower body is so damn still it's crazy
We can watch film all night
But actually facing that move in real life
Will be totally new for us
This is Nationals
That moment when the ball gets spiked
It's not just a one on one battle
Between spiker and blocker
And even if there are two blockers
It's not one on two
It's one guy against six defenders
And there will always be a way to fight
But I guess you don't need me to tell you that
Of course I'm going to try to stop the ball
It's what I do
But I mean it's not like
I'm suddenly going to be better than
One of the best middle blockers in the country
That said
If it's one on six
Then a kill block isn't the only option
Now is it
That's right
They made the right choice there
Not to run around like idiots
Just look if they had run after him
He'd have used it against them
And they could have never locked down his entire range anyway
Get too desperate to stop the ball
And you dig your own grave
Still
Even knowing all this
If it were me
I'd probably get antsy and go for the block anyway
I'm sure I can stop at least a few of them
But with Suki
Well who knows
During the last two sets
He was telling his guys what to watch for
That's how they'll figure out what Tsuna's doing
In volleyball
It's a given that the other team will score on you
It's impossible to ever have a shutout game
There's no perfect strategy against any given attack
But when it comes to this turning spike of Tsuna's
The more he decides to use it
The more it gives the advantage to Suki and the rest of Karasano
Wait
Has he deliberately been blocking only my team
And that's how they'll figure out what Tsuna's doing
In volleyball
It's a given that the other team will score on you
It's impossible to ever have a shutout game
There's no perfect strategy against any given attack
But when it comes to this turning spike of Tsuna's
The more he decides to use it
The more it gives the advantage to Suki and the rest of Karasano
Has he deliberately been blocking only my cross shots?
Hey, thanks for letting me get a nice satisfying hit in every time
Hmph, oh I wanted to thank you as well
For being so predictable
It was deliberate
He has to be the least assertive middle blocker I've ever seen
Does this guy even have a pulse?
I see Karasano has more than just new attacks to throw at their opponent
Things are starting to get a lot less predictable now
Mm-hmm
Hisashi
Go get us ten points
Hmph
This is my last chance in this game
All you man
Hisashi
Be the hero
This is my 28th service ace in my head
I
Don't think he can even hear us
Or anything else for that matter
Not even the other team
All of his attention is on the ball
And where he's aiming
Nice kill Alan
Jump jump Alan
One more time
Yeah
Nice kill Alan
Jump jump Alan
One more time
Nice kill
I saw those intense first years and they were incredible
It made me excited
But it was also like they were a completely different species
But then
Tadashi worked his way up to being a hero
So did Tanaka
And Inoshita got subbed in in an emergency and did better than he ever thought he could
So did Kazuhito
Even if I could never be like Noia or Kageyama
Part of me
Thought I could have my own epic moment on the court
Even if it was time for me
It felt like they were a completely different species
But then
Tadashi worked his way up to being a hero
So did Tanaka
And Inoshita got subbed in in an emergency and did better than he ever thought he could
So did Kazuhito
Even if I could never be like Noia or Kageyama
Even if it was just for a second
I thought I could be a hero
I guess
I guess I was wrong
Sorry guys
That was a fantastic serve Hisashi
You aimed at the perfect spot
Relax
Listen it's not like today is going to be the last chance you'll ever get to go out on a court and crush some poor receiver, okay?
Uh, yeah
But for the third years
Today might really be the last day
And here I am
Doing nothing
You're doing nothing
Yeah!
Alright Kageyama, get it going
It's a left serve
It's a left serve!
Tubio Kageyama has a real gift
It's a left serve
It's a left serve!
Tubio Kageyama has a real gift
Kurasuno's truly on the offensive now
Time out!
Yes!
Two more rotations
And Atsumamiya will be serving again
We need to score as much as we can while we have the chance
So
When I was really little
I was a huge scaredy-cat
Oh?
Huh?
Ah!
I don't remember too well
But I think it lasted until I started grade school
I was scared of bugs
I was scared of birds
I was scared of tricycles
I was scared of ghosts
I think I was pretty shy too
So like uh
In a previous life?
I just said when I was a little kid!
But my gramps was a real
Toss him into the deep end type of guy
So I got over most of my fears
Yeah!
Your gramps is intense!
Hello!
Uh!
Thanks for having me over!
I met him twice
He had a different hottie with him both times
It's rare for Nishinoya to be this chatty during a match
Is it the nurse talking?
When Atsumamiya was serving
It was like my feet were glued to the ground
But it was kind of a familiar feeling
It was that feeling of fear again
Huh?
I'm always impressed when someone can come out and say that they're scared
Okay, so fear was familiar to him
What does this mean?
Well
I doubt we mortals would understand
My gramps?
He was always telling me
It's a waste of life to be scared
Oh!
Not that jackass!
Am I getting all ready?
It's good!
Eat it!
Make sure you really do hate a food
Instead of just assuming you'll hate it
Don't go in from above and don't look him in the eye
No, there's always a reason when someone is hostile
My feet won't reach!
Once you learn something new, see how far you can go
It's such a waste to let your life end without ever really living
Yeah, but...
Well, what if it's still scary?
Well, that's easy
If it's still scary
You get someone to help you
Yeah, but...
Well, what if it's still scary?
Well, that's easy
If it's still scary
You get someone to help you
Bring it on!
Look at those itty-bitty little hands
I'm gonna not know how far you can go
It's such a waste to let your life end without ever really living
Yeah, but...
Well, what if it's still scary?
Well, that's easy
If it's still scary
You get someone to help you
Bring it on!
Look at those itty-bitty little hands
I'm gonna knock him off!
Ah!
Say, Nishinoya
You don't have to force yourself to get good at all these things
That's easy
If it's still scary
You get someone to help you
Bring it on!
Look at those itty-bitty little hands
I'm gonna knock him off!
Ah!
Say, Nishinoya
You don't have to force yourself to get good at overhands.
I'm pretty sure you can still get by with your underhand receives.
Honestly, I used to think it'd be sweet to receive every ball underhanded.
Thought I could pull it off, too.
But I can still go higher.
And now that I know I have options available to not try them all out, well, that'd be boring.
Nishinoya! Move closer!
Nice work!
Yeah!
Nice kill!
There we go.
Alright!
Nice one, nice one!
Karasuno managed to stop a Tsubumiya after just one serve!
Yeah!
Time!
He's huge!
He sure is.
Apparently his name is Alan and he's in fifth grade.
He's so cool!
I'm so jealous.
I wish I had a western name!
That's why you're jealous?
Maybe I can get it legally changed.
You can't just change your name like that.
It'll make grandma really sad.
Oh, yeah.
Morons.
Wait!
Osamu!
Samu!
Yeah, and that makes you Sumu!
These two are weirdos.
That's too cool!
No, it's not!
Hey there, young man!
My name is Inuhata.
I am super happy so many of you showed up here to learn about volleyball with me today.
I knew the two of them long before they got to be so famous.
Oh, Setter?
Man, I wanted to see a spiker play.
Ugh, those two are so rude.
Think Jeeba would teach us?
Yeah, right, dummy.
Come on, don't be stupid.
Only the best players get to play Setter.
That's what makes it the coolest position.
So does that mean you want to be a Setter, Salo?
No, I want a Spike.
What was your point, then?
Wow, nice kill.
That's pretty impressive.
Dude, I hit that last one, like, perfectly.
Yeah?
Don't be scared, come on.
I'm going to help you get the ball right over.
Whoa, nice job!
We're going to work on this.
Setters...
Hmm?
Are so cool!
Ah!
Hmm?
It's Alan!
Hi!
Hey, twins!
I'd say the twins weren't really good, so much as they were powerful,
with an extra healthy dose of competitiveness.
Ah!
If I had to say, Osamu was just a shade better than Atsumu,
so it was common to see Atsumu challenging him to duels.
Osamu, try playing Setter.
Well, I mean, only the best players get to be the Setter,
so what did you expect?
But I got the feeling that Atsumu had something that went beyond just that hatred of losing.
All right, well, okay, Atsumu, you set today.
Huh?
Don't you know, Atsumu, the more positions you play, the better and more well-rounded you get.
Ah, shut up and be jealous, Samu!
Atsumu was a better Setter every time I saw him.
And when he was paired with Osamu, they were perfect.
Eventually, people started fearing the MIA Twins.
I was, like, so on my game today.
The way the ball felt in my hands out there, how it felt when it left.
I could totally see what their blockers were doing, too.
Did you guys have a problem with my sets?
Not...
really.
Then why exactly couldn't you score any points?
What the hell is this problem?
Well, he's good.
You blame him?
He's just so full of himself.
We do tend to win any time we have both of them on their game.
Just deal with it.
Sumu, the other guys don't like you.
Yep, so what?
I made up my mind.
I'm never gonna be like you.
I'm going to be nice to others.
What are you even talking about, you idiot?
I've known the twins since we were kids.
But sometimes, Atsumu scared me.
It's supposed to be exhausting when other people don't like you.
Especially people on your own team.
Osamu, you were really screwing up today.
Well, we all have our off days.
Shake it off.
Look, we all suck at this game, okay?
That's the whole reason we come in here and practice.
Nice, bad duck.
You're a useless piece of trash.
A piece of trash that can't score even when he's given such perfect sets.
You should quit now and let someone else try the position.
Come on, Atsumu.
That was a little harsh, man.
Osamu already feels bad enough already.
What?
Damn it.
You abusive, tyrannical pig!
Everybody knows there are times when you might be on your game, but the rest of us just aren't, okay?
Hey, hey, you two, stop it.
Somebody's gonna get hurt.
That's simple, you stupid ass of the guy.
They really don't hold back, do they?
Talk at all.
Does Whittle Atsumu never make any mistakes at all?
What's wrong with calling a piece of trash a piece of trash?
Look in the mirror, some type dumpster.
Why don't you just go live in the dumpster where you belong?
What the hell is it just saying to me?
I'm glad I hate you.
Do it, bro.
Let me go!
Want to play winning 11?
Yeah.
Slow down, you stupid idiots!
If you ask me, the biggest blessing Atsumu has isn't his physique, or even any of his various talents.
It's actually Osamu.
No matter how fast the two of them run, if no one else can catch up, they will always catch up with each other.
I'm sure that can be annoying sometimes.
Come back here, you scrub!
But the more they compete with each other, the stronger they get.
All Japan youth intensive, eh? Not bad, Sumo.
You should be more upset, Samu!
I am, you dumbass. I'm upset at the fact that I'm not more upset about it, honestly.
You've been working hard your whole life, Sumo.
What the hell? You'd better not be telling me you haven't been working this whole damn time!
I think they wanted someone like you.
Someone who is a hard worker and is a little bit crazy.
When it comes to skill, we're equal.
Nah, everyone knows I'm better!
Did you let me finish?
It's just...
You love volleyball.
You do.
And you love it more than me.
It's slowing down.
Follow through!
Chins fall!
Damn, that's gonna be tough!
Sorry!
Follow!
I wonder how many people in the crowd actually noticed how incredible that set was.
Usually in these situations, the setter would use an underhand pass to send it high up to the left.
Yeah!
So this is what an all-Japan youth setter can do.
I'm really amazed that you set a ball from that low.
You could just go underhanded.
No, I couldn't, because I'm the setter and it's my job to set.
I'm responsible for getting the ball to the best spot.
So?
So, underhand, I only have my two arms.
Overhand, I've got ten fingers.
I want the most contact points to get better support.
Cause I'm a setter!
That's Atsumumiya for ya.
He may be something of a goof, and sometimes he can be stubborn and overbearing.
But for his spikers, he's the most considerate, self-sacrificing player I know.
He's the picture-perfect setter.
Yeah?
Me?
I could never pull that off.
I don't have the speed nor the reflexes to get under a ball like that last one.
Not that quickly, anyway.
I don't have the muscle to hold my body steady in such a low posture.
And I don't have the skill to set the ball that perfectly under those circumstances.
I'm already well aware of the stuff you can't do.
Me too.
I'm glad we made it here.
I don't have the skill to hold my body steady in such a low posture.
Yeah?
I don't have the skill to hold my body steady in such a low determinism.
See you next time.
Bye.